Hello friends, I am Ankur Upadhyay,
welcome to your own
YouTube channel Share Market Analysis.
Friends, here there is some good
news from the government for the company
whose name is Godrej Aggregate. Now
look at this stock, if you are Nivedita, then
you must have seen that there was a big jump in today's session.
However, the
stock has come down from the upper level and has
banded again. But a
very good news has come for the stock which
I am sharing with you all. Look, the
price of the stock is closing at the level of 49 i.e. 499.
Today's high of 50030 was set in the stock. The 52
week high of 57 is live. Brother,
such stocks which are almost around ₹750 are
getting a lot of collection from there. The technical
chart pattern is suggesting that
if the levels of 520 which have already come today are crossed,
then there will be a big rise.
Now let us understand what news has come for the company.
After that, the
quarterly numbers of NTs have come, I will discuss that too
with all of you, so let's start and move ahead.
First of all, if we talk about Godrej Agro
Veterinary, then the
government has given them 47000 acres of land in Telangana so that they
can expand their palm oil business, so
this is big breaking news for this company.
Now see, the company is
getting land for its business, so definitely
when land is available for business, then
business means palm oil and they will produce it, they will
find it, then the income,
revenue, profit, everything will increase. I think
this is a breaking news, I will
share with you, exactly what is
happening, the company has been allotted
potential area of
47000 Sangha Reddy district of Telangana by the
Department of Agriculture and Cooperation,
Government of Telangana, so big news has come
and after that the price of stock also rose very fast,
you can trade trading by about 8.2%. At
that time, the stock had fallen by 8.9% as soon as the news came.
Current Li  Only 5.5% has been
banded with DJ.
Oil pump business expansion on Telangana government allotted land. So
this news has come, it is visible for this stock
and this stock is already there. I will talk to all of you
once that it looks good, the
stock also looks good, the valuation in terms of oil is good at
31 for long term purpose.
If someone has the stock, it is not giving any special returns.
Deep definitely has
big relief in between, so whenever there is a big DI,
then take it, like I invested a loan of Rs 300 in Kovid, from
there the stock went straight to Rs 750. If
you look at it recently also, it was
Rs 400 in March 2023 and from there it has gone up to Rs 550. So
whenever it comes down, then
you can find opportunities to average it. Rest it is easy to
say, it is very difficult to do. I
know that it does not happen, all these things move forward. If we
talk about other stocks, then we have seen the company's numbers coming as well.  The
company has
also won a deal for 5 years, so I will
share that with you too. First let's talk about profit, the
consolidated net profit has been
reduced from ₹340 crore to ₹300.11 crore
quarter on quarter, but the market estimate is
exactly ₹300.11 crore, so you will say
that Nick, this is a hero case, these are the line numbers,
profit figures, if we talk about revenue, then there is
revenue of ₹2300 crore against ₹2371 crore, so if we talk about
water based revenue in the quarter, then the
company has presented revenue of ₹395 crore against approximately ₹423 crore and there is a
hockey like decline in margins as well,
from 17.86% the
margins have been reduced to 17.18%, if that is seen then there is
not much major decline to be seen, hockey hockey
direction has been seen in the numbers, the expectations in the numbers were
also something like this, but the
good thing is that a breaking news for the company
which  It has come, look, I am going to share it with you. The
company has won an order of approximately
$50 million. I want to share with you an X total amount. The company has won a $50 million
high-tech deal agreement for a five-year
tenure, meaning the company has won a deal worth about $50 million for five years. This
news is coming, the
overall stock results are good. Now we have a
weaver who
wants to talk about RBL Bank stock. Look, RBL Bank,
first of all, your selection did not seem right to me.
When investing in a bank, I
always prefer to stay in a large cap or a
bank which you are seeing is growing
very fast. Now if we talk about RBL, it has
not made any money for the investors in the long term. There is
RBL, there is Bandhan, there are two-three such
banks which are just banks,
not making money for anyone. Now, if we
talk about RBL, then recently you
see a lot of growth. Show the technical structure in the stock from ₹144 to approximately ₹230
levels.  It is
looking quite strong, I
want to say clear cut,
leave it for long term purpose but it is
good for technical i.e. short term. Now I would like to
share an SLR with you in the stock
with a stop loss. This is bringing you the stock to
149, 10% below this level from here.
Before that, there is some such part on one side. The
stock has gone straight from ₹200 to ₹224 and is
currently consolidating. Until it
breaks the previous swing low, which is a double
line, I think you should
not sell the stock. Rest you
can also manage your position according to your bike. It is
looking strong right now. The chart pattern is
almost there. If you do a trailer sale, then I
think the stock can show a journey of up to ₹250 for you.
So this
was a video from my side for you, you must have understood and
liked it. Thank you. So,
watching this video on match has been great.